trapster.com 2013-12-26

# Trapster® - Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

_Effective date: July 2011_

We take your trust seriously, and our goal is to safeguard your privacy while providing you with the best possible experience using the Trapster service (the “Service”).  Reach Unlimited Corporation and its parents and affiliates (collectively, “Reach Unlimited”) provide this notice explaining our information collection practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used when you access content via our mobile applications or through our website, located at http://www.trapster.com. 

#### What We Collect

When you register for the Service, Reach Unlimited will ask you to provide an email address and, optionally, a user name.  You may also, in using other functions of the Service such as creating a user profile, have the option of provide your name, address, phone number, photo, or other information (collectively, with user name and email address, “Personal Information”) .

Reach Unlimited also may collect certain technical information when you visit our website or access our Service through a mobile application, such as the type of device or browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider, aggregate data about the number of visits to a site or Service, and/or aggregate data about the pages visited.  We may combine information we receive via the Service with other information you have provided to us and with information from other sources to improve our knowledge of you as a user, to help us provide quality customer service, to provide and customize our Service, and to offer certain other products and services to you subject to your marketing preferences.

If you enable location services in our mobile applications, Reach Unlimited collects location data from your device, including latitude and longitude, speed and heading (collectively, “Location Information”).

#### How We Use the Information

Except as otherwise indicated, Reach Unlimited uses the Personal Information you provide:

  * to enable customization of your user experience when using the Service;
  * to enable you to share information (including Location Information) with other users of the Service and on other platforms such as Twitter and Facebook;
  * to communicate with you and to assist you with any questions you have about the Service;
  * to offer you other products or services that may be of interest to you;
  * to ease use of our Service by eliminating the need to re-enter information; and
  * to display content and advertising customized to your interests and preferences.
  * to create higher quality of service

Except as otherwise indicated, Reach Unlimited uses Location Information:

  * to provide content relevant to your locations and routes;
  * to enable you to store your trip information in our Trips feature and
  * to enable you to share location information with buddies through our Caravan feature.

Authorized Reach Unlimited service providers and contractors may have access to your information to facilitate its use consistent with this Policy.  Personal Information and Location Information may be used to assist us in the development of new features and services and/or the improvement of our existing Service; to cooperate with government officials or parties in litigation under process of law or regulation, or as otherwise required or permitted by law; to protect the security or integrity of the Service, and/or to enforce the terms governing its use; to protect against a threat of safety or destruction of property; and/or to protect against legal liability.

Reach Unlimited may anonymize and/or aggregate Personal Information and Location Information so that it does not identify you, and this anonymized and/or aggregated information may be used and stored for any purpose, without limitation.  These purposes may include, but are not limited to, generating reporting, conducting research and analysis, and improving the design and content of our Service, and Reach Unlimited may share this data with contractors, partners, and other third-parties.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Reach Unlimited may disclose Personal Information and/or Location Information we maintain about you to non-affiliated third parties under the following types of circumstances:  when we have your permission to do so; to comply with the law, or when we respond to a subpoena or other process, legal order, or official request; as otherwise required by law; to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or, as permitted by applicable law, when we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of the legal terms that govern your use of the Service.  In addition, Reach Unlimited may transfer Personal Information, Location Information and non-personally identifiable information if Reach Unlimited is acquired by or merged with another company.

#### Your Marketing Preferences

We generally ask you for your marketing preferences at the time we collect your information.  If you wish to change your marketing preferences, please visit your account page on our website.  You can also opt-out from most messages by sending an email from the email account associated with your registration to contact@trapster.com. Some mandatory service messages are required for use of the Service, and are not subject to opt-out.

#### Security

Reach Unlimited has implemented security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse and alteration of any information under our control.

#### IP Addresses and Cookies

Like other websites, the Trapster website uses your domain, IP address and browser information to help diagnose problems with our Service and equipment, to administer the Service, and for security purposes. "Cookies" are pieces of data sent from a Web server to a Web browser that enable a Web server to identify users that visit a site hosted by that server. Reach Unlimited may use Cookies and other similar technologies in order to identify you so that we can provide more customized information and services to you. In addition, advertisers on our Service may place their own Cookies. In general, if you choose, you can disable the use of Cookies by reviewing your browser's preferences and options.

#### International Transfer

As the Trapster Service is available worldwide, it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally.  In particular, information is generally transferred to and processed in the United States.  Data protection laws vary between the United States and other jurisdictions.  Please be assured that we take reasonable steps so that your privacy is protected.

#### Modification of Privacy Policy

Reach Unlimited may change this Privacy Policy at any time, and will notify you in an appropriate manner, such as by posting the changed or amended Privacy Policy on our Service.

#### Viewing or Updating your Information

To ensure that you have as much control over your Personal Information as possible, you may update your information by contacting us via our Contact page below. We will use reasonable efforts to process any change you make; provided, however, that requests to delete information are subject to our internal reporting and retention policies and all applicable legal obligations.

#### Questions

If you have questions about this Policy or about how information we collect is used by Reach Unlimited, please visit our Contact page at http://www.trapster.com/contact.php.

Reach Unlimited Corp.  
5963 La Place Court, Suite 200  
Carlsbad, CA 92008
